bridge.co.za 2018-06-10

# Privacy Policy – Bridge Loans

Bridge respects (and is committed to protecting) your privacy. Bridge thus takes extraordinary steps to handle any personal information collected on this website only in ways compatible with this Privacy Policy.

This website may collect certain information about your visit ? such as the name of the internet service provider and the internet protocol (IP) address through which you access the internet, the date and time you access the site, the page(s) that you visit while on the site, and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to this site.

Bridge is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. Bridge does not (or will never) sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in the privacy statement below. This information is only used to administer this website, analyse trends and to generally help improve this site, and will never result in your receiving of spam e-mails.

### Log Files:

Bridge keeps log files on broad fields to track user movements, analyse trends and gather demographic data. This is not linked to a visitor?s personal identification in any way.

### Cookies / Tracking Technology:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor?s hard drive containing information about the visitor. Cookies and tracking technologies are useful for gathering information, such as browser types and operating systems, tracking the number of visitors to a website and understanding how visitors use the websites they browse. This information can help customise a website for specific users. Advertisers connected to Bridge might at times require cookies to track statistics about products and locations, but they will not be supplied with any personal identification details of users. However, Bridge generally uses cookies for login convenience only.

### Links:

This Privacy Policy applies solely to Bridge. Bridge is not necessarily aware of, nor are responsible for, differences in privacy statements of external websites linked to or from ours.

### Newsletter Registration:

Visitors who registered to receive the Bridge newsletter can unsubscribe to this service at any time. Any personal information stored in the Bridge database related to the newsletter subscription will be treated as confidential and will never be shared or sold to any third party.

### Sharing:

Bridge does not harvest the information of third parties when visitors share a page of this website in social circles.

### Competitions:

If, at any particular time, Bridge conducts contests or competitions for visitors, participation is voluntary and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter the contest. Collected data is used to notify the winner(s) and to award the prize(s).

### Changes To This Policy:

Bridge may need to update this policy from time to time, in order to address new issues and reflect changes on this website. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

_Continued use of this website signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy._
